Guide to the First Presbyterian Church of Ithaca records,1801-2010.
First Presbyterian Church of Ithaca records
- Additional material from March 2006
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1860-1861 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1862-1865 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1866-1867 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1868 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1869 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1870 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Certificates RESTRICTED, 1871-1872 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Treasurer Papers RESTRICTED, 1911-1919 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous Treasurer Papers, 1915-1916, 1918 RESTRICTED, 1915-1918 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Treasurer Reports RESTRICTED, 1917-1928 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Receipts and Receipts with Thank-you letters RESTRICTED, 1914 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Receipts and Receipts with Thank-you letters RESTRICTED, 1915 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Receipts and Receipts with Thank-you letters RESTRICTED, 1916 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and Receipts with Thank-you letters RESTRICTED, 1917 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Receipts RESTRICTED, 1918 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Synodical Home Missions Correspondence and Receipts RESTRICTED, 1914-1917 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Receipts RESTRICTED, 1915-1918 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Books: 9/16/1924-10/28/1925, 11/4/1925-3/13/27, 3/21/1927-2/7/1928, 2/14/1928-12/31/1928, 1/7/1928-10/15/1929, 10/22/1929-8/6/1930 RESTRICTED, 1924-1930 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Books: 8/6/1930-5/18/1931, 5/24/1931-4/25/1932, 5/2/1932-3/27/1933, 3/31/1933-1/14/1934, 1/22/1934-8/23/1934, 8/30/1934-6/10/1935, 1/6/1936-9/21/1936 RESTRICTED, 1930-1936 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Cancelled Checks RESTRICTED, 1894 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1904, 1915 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1916 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1917 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Expenses/Bills RESTRICTED, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Library Fund RESTRICTED, 1917 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Subscriptions for Church Anniversary Book RESTRICTED, 1904 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Tompkins County National Bank Account of E. Plathert RESTRICTED, 1888-1895 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Tompkins County National Bank RESTRICTED, 1912-1919 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Tompkins County National Bank of E. Gilbert RESTRICTED, 1901-1912 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Passbooks First National Bank, 1898-1913, 1923 RESTRICTED, 1898-1923 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Passbooks Ithaca Savings Bank, 1922, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Passbook: "New Era Fund" RESTRICTED, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Ithaca Trust Company "New Era Fund" RESTRICTED, 1919-1920 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Annual Statements, 1892, 1902, 1904-1911, 1913-1914 RESTRICTED, 1892-1914 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 4/1/1922-4/1/1923 RESTRICTED, 1922-1923 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Pledge Books for 1898-1899 Construction, 1898-1901, 1899 RESTRICTED, 1898-1899 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Documents: Horton Poor Fund RESTRICTED, 1906 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: J. A. Sanford will RESTRICTED, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: C. C. Crawford will RESTRICTED, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: Charlotte E. Williams bequest RESTRICTED, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: E. C. Stewart part of will pertaining to Church RESTRICTED (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: Lorraine W. Platts bequest RESTRICTED, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: Nancy L. Beers bequest, 1923, 1928 RESTRICTED, 1923-1928 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: Helen M. Tuthill bequest RESTRICTED, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: Mary E. Fleming will RESTRICTED, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: Harriet C. Davis will RESTRICTED, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: Louise Everett Storms will RESTRICTED (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: Harriet N. Williams will RESTRICTED, 1912 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Document: A. J. Brown will RESTRICTED, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: Stewart Fund, 1923-1924, 1926 RESTRICTED, 1923-1926 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Documents: Deacon’s Charity Fund, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - R. B. Williams: documents relating to Trusts, Bequests, 1883, 1923, 1935 RESTRICTED, 1883-1935 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Church Matters: Annual Reports RESTRICTED, 1872 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Church Matters: Pew Rents, 1869, 1891 RESTRICTED, 1869-1891 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Church Matters: Pledge List RESTRICTED, 1873 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Church Matters: Correspondence, 1873, 1875 RESTRICTED, 1873-1875 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Church Matters: Deposit Slips RESTRICTED, 1895 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Every Member Canvass RESTRICTED, 1931-1937 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Every Member Canvass, Special Committee - F. C. [Finance Committee] RESTRICTED, 1931-1932 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Every Member Canvass RESTRICTED, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Every Member Canvass - Campaign Pledges RESTRICTED, 1932 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Every Member Canvass RESTRICTED, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Every Member Canvass RESTRICTED, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Every Member Canvass RESTRICTED, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Every Member Canvass - Resource Materials, 1932-1933, 1936 RESTRICTED, 1932-1936 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Every Member Canvass - General RESTRICTED, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Every Member Canvass - Canvasser Materials RESTRICTED, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Every Member Canvass - General Notes RESTRICTED, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Survey (Budgets, etc.) RESTRICTED, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Membership Lists by Districts RESTRICTED, 1928-1929 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Every Member Canvass, Pledge Campaign RESTRICTED, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Every Member Canvass, Pledge Campaign RESTRICTED, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Every Member Canvass, Pledge Campaign: Returns RESTRICTED, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Every Member Canvass, Pledge Campaign RESTRICTED, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - Every Member Canvass, Pledge Campaign RESTRICTED, 1928-1929 (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Every Member Canvass, Pledge Campaign RESTRICTED, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - Woman’s Association Expense Account RESTRICTED, 1931-1947 (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - Envelope Account Books, Vols. I, II RESTRICTED, 1898-1899 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Envelope Account Books, Vol. III RESTRICTED, 1900 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Envelope Account Books, Vol. IV RESTRICTED (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Envelope Account Books, Vol. V RESTRICTED, 1906 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Envelope Account Books, Vol. VI RESTRICTED, 1909 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Envelope Account Books, Vol. VII RESTRICTED (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Woman’s Aid Society First Presbyterian Church Treasurer’s Book RESTRICTED, 1912-1925 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements RESTRICTED, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Financial Statements RESTRICTED, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Statements of Trusts RESTRICTED, 1959-1970 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Statements of Trusts RESTRICTED, 1971-1980 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Endowed Funds RESTRICTED, 1959-1980 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - 4 cancelled checks of Miss Ch. Williams RESTRICTED, 1920-1922 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Woman’s Missionary Society Annual Treasurer’s Reports, 1909-1912, 1914-1919 RESTRICTED, 1909-1919 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - List of Presidents of Woman’s Aid RESTRICTED, 1896-1917 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Westminster Guild RESTRICTED, 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Seneca Street Manse, 1958, 1962 RESTRICTED, 1958-1962 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Finance materials, 1918-1919, 1965 RESTRICTED, 1918, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Notes and letters re pastoral nominations, 1919, RESTRICTED, 1919 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/4/1943-3/1944 RESTRICTED, 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1945-3/31/1946 RESTRICTED, 1945-1946 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1947-4/1/1948 RESTRICTED, 1947-1948 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1948-4/1/1949 RESTRICTED, 1948-1949 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1949-4/1/1950 RESTRICTED, 1949-1950 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1952-3/31/1953 RESTRICTED, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1953-4/1/1954 RESTRICTED, 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Pledge Accounts, 4/1/1954-4/1/1955 RESTRICTED, 1954-1955 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Youth Budget Accounts RESTRICTED (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Manual of First Presbyterian Church, Ithaca, N.Y., Adopted 4/9/1931 RESTRICTED, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Pledges and Similar Payments RESTRICTED, 1975-1991 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger RESTRICTED, 1975-1993 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Operating Accounts RESTRICTED, 1975-1980 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Cash Receipts RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Cash Receipts RESTRICTED, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Cash Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements RESTRICTED, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Finance Miscellaneous RESTRICTED, 1980-1985 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Payroll Records RESTRICTED, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Payroll Records RESTRICTED, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - TCTC Year end deposits RESTRICTED, 1981-1985 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - General Ledger April 1966-1970 (Old System) I RESTRICTED, 1966-1970 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - General Ledger April 1966-1970 (Old System) II RESTRICTED, 1966-1970 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - General Ledger April 1966-1970 (Old System) III RESTRICTED, 1966-1970 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Capital Funds Campaign 1967-1971 I RESTRICTED, 1967-1971 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Capital Funds Campaign 1967-1971 II RESTRICTED, 1967-1971 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Trustee Meetings minutes RESTRICTED, 1937-1953 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Check Stubs RESTRICTED, 1951-1960 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Westminster Foundation RESTRICTED, 1939-1964 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - World Wide Restoration Fund RESTRICTED, 1945-1949 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Finances RESTRICTED, 1930-1960 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee RESTRICTED, 1932-1967 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Receipted Bills RESTRICTED, 1945-1946 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Receipted Bills RESTRICTED, 1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Receipted Bills RESTRICTED, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Cancelled Checks RESTRICTED, 1944-1946 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence Treasurer RESTRICTED, 1957-1968 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - TCTC Correspondence, Forms, Agreement RESTRICTED, 1959-1975 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Bills Paid, 1944, 1944-1945, 1945-1947 (3 vols.) RESTRICTED, 1944-1947 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Benevolences RESTRICTED, 1930 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Session minutes, reports: 1926-1927; Session Fund, 1930 RESTRICTED, 1926-1930 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Trustees Fund RESTRICTED, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Trustees Fund RESTRICTED, 1930-1931 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Sunday School Reserve Fund RESTRICTED, 1922 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Portland Point S. S. Benevolences Account RESTRICTED, 1922-1939 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Classes and Departments RESTRICTED (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Envelope Fund, Session Fund, Church Library, Reserve Fund, S. S. Library RESTRICTED, 1913 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer’s Accounts: Benevolent Fund, Manse Fund Pledges RESTRICTED, 1913 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Church Funds RESTRICTED, 1898-1911 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Budgets RESTRICTED, 1953-1970 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Finance Reports RESTRICTED, 1952-1962 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Finance Reports RESTRICTED, 1959-1972 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1969; Financial and Organization RESTRICTED, 1963-1969 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Finance Committee, #1 RESTRICTED, 1964-1968 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Finance Committee, # 2 RESTRICTED, 1963-1969 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1960-1069 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, 1969-1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Finance RESTRICTED, Past-1971 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Finance: Budgets RESTRICTED, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Finance: Monthly Statements RESTRICTED, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee RESTRICTED, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Finance Committee RESTRICTED, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Accounts RESTRICTED, 1972-1974 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer’s Reports RESTRICTED, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer’s Reports RESTRICTED, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer’s Reports RESTRICTED, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer’s Reports RESTRICTED, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer’s Reports RESTRICTED, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer’s Reports RESTRICTED, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - 50 Million Fund RESTRICTED, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - 50 Million Fund, UPC (US) Payments RESTRICTED, 1969-1981 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - The D.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1932-1933 (Box 63, Folder v.1)
  - The D.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1933-1934 (Box 63, Folder v.2)
  - The D.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1934-1935 (Box 63, Folder v.3)
  - The D.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1935-1936 (Box 63, Folder v.4)
  - The D.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1936-1937 (Box 63, Folder v.5)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1923 (Box 63, Folder v.1)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1924 (Box 63, Folder v.2)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1925 (Box 63, Folder v.3)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1927-1928 (Box 63, Folder v.4)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1928-1929 (Box 63, Folder v.5)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1929-1930 (Box 63, Folder v.6)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1930-1931 (Box 63, Folder v.7)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1931-1932 (Box 63, Folder v.8)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1931-1932 (Box 63, Folder v.9)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1932 (Box 63, Folder v.10)
  - The S.S. Church Treasurer’s Record RESTRICTED, 1932-1933 (Box 63, Folder v.11)
  - Receipts/Disbursements, 10/1911-11/1913 RESTRICTED, 1911-1913 (Box 63, Folder bd.w/)
  - Poor Fund RESTRICTED, 1911-1914 (Box 63, Folder bd.w/)
  - Arrears RESTRICTED, 1912 (Box 63, Folder bd.w/)
  - Interest Account RESTRICTED, 1912 (Box 63, Folder bd.w/)
  - Annual Statements RESTRICTED, 1910-1911 (Box 63, Folder bd.w/)
  - Annual Report RESTRICTED, 1912 (Box 63, Folder bd.w/)
  - Receipts Book I, Nos. 1-125 A-Fla. RESTRICTED, 1930-1931 (Box 63, Folder Bk. I)
  - Receipts Book II, Nos. 126-250 For-Mor. RESTRICTED, 1930-1931 (Box 63, Folder Bk. II)
  - Receipts Book III, Nos. 251-375 Mor-Tan. RESTRICTED, 1930-1931 (Box 64, Folder Bk. III)
  - Receipts Book IV, Nos. 376-500 Tan-Z and Misc. RESTRICTED, 1930-1931 (Box 64, Folder Bk. IV)
  - Benevolent Account, 9/1913-6/1922 RESTRICTED, 1913-1922 (Box 64, Folder bd.w/)
  - Maintenance Account, 9/1913-8/1922 RESTRICTED, 1913-1922 (Box 64, Folder bd.w/)
  - Receipts 1929-1930 Bk. I, #1-101, A-Gra RESTRICTED, 1929-1930 (Box 65, Folder Bk. I)
  - Receipts 1929-1930 Bk. II, #102-204, Gre-Pea RESTRICTED, 1929-1930 (Box 65, Folder Bk. II)
  - Receipts 1929-1930 Bk. III, #205-302, Pearson-Underwood RESTRICTED, 1929-1930 (Box 65, Folder Bk. III)
  - Receipts 1929-1930 Bk. IV, #303-499, Van Arsdale- RESTRICTED, 1929-1930 (Box 65, Folder Bk. IV)
  - Receipts 1929-1930 Bk. V, #500-545, Pledged but not using envelopes RESTRICTED, 1929-1930 (Box 65, Folder Bk. V)
  - Ideal "D. E." Record, Vol. I, 10/1913-9/1915, 1913-1915 (Box 66, Folder Vol. I)
  - Ideal "D. E." Record, Vol. II, 10/1915-9/1917, 1915-1917 (Box 66, Folder Vol. II)
  - Ideal "D. E." Record, Vol. III, 10/1917-9/1918, 1917-1918 (Box 66, Folder Vol. III)
  - Ideal "D. E." Record, Vol. IV, 10/1919-9/1920, 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder Vol. IV)
  - Ideal "D. E." Record, Vol. V, 10/1920-9/1922, 1920-1922 (Box 66, Folder Vol. V)
  - "The Seven Last Words of Christ" - phonograph record of a concert at the church, ca. 1951; SR-9774
    -Recorded by the Cornell Recording Service of the Cornell Radio Guild, Inc.
  - Floor plan, 106 E. Court St. (preliminary sketch), 1957 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - Floor plan negative, 114 Catherine St., City assessment map, 106, 110, 114, 1962 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - E. Court St., (2 copies) (Map-case Folder 1)
  - Floor plans and plans for kitchen remodeling, 114 E. Court St., 1962 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - Floor plan for Church, 4 drawings: plans for Church electrical system, 1968 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Chart of Church pews, 3rd ediface, Presbyterian Church FRAGILE (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Preliminary drawing Church floor plans, 1967 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - City Assessment map showing 106, 110, 114 E. Court St., 1956 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Preliminary plans, Westminster Manor, Home for the Elderly;, Auburn, NY, 1968 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Plans for Church, room and door schedules and others, 1968 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Floor plan 106 E. Court St., 1957 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Plans (small scale) 106 E. Court St., 1957 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Plans for fireplace, date and place unknown (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Map of properties owned by First Presbyterian Church, 1962 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Proposed alterations, 1955 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Church seat change, 1998 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Plans First Presbyterian Church alterations: room and door schedules, elevations, structural, heating and ventilating, plumbing, electrical, c. 1068 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - Blueprints and maps (on file, 1964): a list of maps and blueprints of church buildings and grounds, 1964 (Map-case Folder 4)
  - Plans for proposed church (never built), 1892 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - Plans of 2nd and 3rd level of Church [on backing (2)], c. 1967 (Map-case Folder 6)
  - Map "The Contribution of Presbyterian National Missions to the Making of a Christian America", 1927 (Map-case Folder 7)
  - Floor plans - Missionary Apartments, 114 Catherine St. (17 drawings), 1950 (Map-case Folder 8)
  - Detailed drawings of 1935, 1892 Presbyterian Church, 1892, 1935 (Map-case Folder 9-15)
  - Preliminary Renovation Plans, 1st Presbyterian Church, Ithaca NY, undated (Map-case Folder 16)
- Kay-Billie-Klaer (KBK) Academy, Ghana
  - KBK Misc., various (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Notes/lists of books sent to KBK, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Akrofi and Awo Dzietror correspondence, 1986-1995 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Akrofi and Awo Dzietror correspondence, 1995-2010 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Contains 2004 Good News article
  - 1st Prize-giving Day, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Cards made by students, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - "Learning Made Easy Through Latin", Vol. 1, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    By Frank Amfo Sackey and Akrofi Dzietror
  - KBK School Complex Plan; 4 classroom construction and financial statement, 1995 and 1997 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Home Science Center (picture scans), 1998 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Photo album, 1996-1997 (Box 67)
    Construction KBK Academy
  - Photo album, undated (Box 67)
    KBK photos
  - Videos and DVDs of/about KBK, undated (Box 67)
  - 3 Ghanian dresses, MU-1371 - 1373 (Box 68)